Guide to the Vassar College Subject Files, 1864–2023
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- V. C. Blegen Professorship, see: V. C. Departments. Classics
- V. C. Blood Bank, see also: V. C. Blue Cross Community Blood Program (Folder 6.31)
- V. C. Blue Cross Community Blood Program (Folder 6.32)
- V. C. Boat Ride ("Mary Powell") (Folder 6.33)
- V. C. Boats (Folder 6.34)
- V. C. Bookworm (Folder 6.35)
- V. C. Bootjack (gift of Matthew Vassar, Jr.) (Folder 6.36)
- V. C. Buildings (General) (Folder 6.37-6.41)
- V. C. Buildings. ALANA Center, see: V. C. Buildings. Intercultural Center
- V. C. Buildings. Alumnae Gymnasium (Folder 6.42)
- V. C. Buildings. Antolini House (Folder 6.43)
- V. C. Buildings. Avery (Folder 6.44)
- V. C. Buildings. Baldwin House (Folder 6.45)
- V. C. Buildings. Barns (Folder 6.46)
- V. C. Buildings. Blodgett (Folder 6.47)
- V. C. Buildings. Buildings and Grounds Service Center (Folder 6.48)
- V. C. Buildings. Calistenium, see: V. C. Buildings. Avery
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel (Folder 6.49)
- V. C. Buildings. Chaplain's House (Folder 6.50)
- V. C. Buildings. Chicago Hall (Folder 6.51)
- V. C. Buildings. Class of 1915 Observatory, see: V. C. Buildings Observatory
- V. C. Buildings. Cushing (Folder 6.52)
- V. C. Buildings. Davison (Folder 6.53)
- V. C. Buildings. Doubleday Art Studio (formerly Facility Operations) (Folder 6.53A)
- V. C. Buildings. Ely, see also: V. C. Buildings Alumnae Gymnasium (Aula) (Folder 6.54)
- V. C. Buildings. Ferry House (Dexter M.) (Folder 6.55)
- V. C. Buildings. Field House see: V. C. Buildings Walker...
- V. C. Buildings. Josselyn (Folder 6.56)
- V. C. Buildings. Kendrick (Folder 6.57)
- V. C. Buildings. Kenyon (Folder 6.58-6.59)
- V. C. Buildings. Laundry (Folder 6.60)
- V. C. Buildings. Lockwood see: V. C. Libraries. Buildings.
- V. C. Buildings. Lodge (i.e. Gate) (Folder 6.61)
- V. C. Buildings. Loeb Art Center (Folder 6.62)
- V. C. Buildings. Lyman (Folder 6.63)
- V. C. Buildings. Main (general) (Folder 6.64)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Breaking ground (Folder 6.65)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Browsing Room (Folder 6.66)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Clock (Folder 6.67)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. College Center, incl. Co-op Bookstore, Computer Store and Gallery (Folder 6.68)
- V. C. Building. Main. Fire, see: V. C. Fires
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Tefft, proposed plans, perspective (facsimile) (Folder 6.69)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Thompson Annex (Folder 6.70)
- V. C. Buildings. Mudd Chemistry Building (Seeley G.) (Folder 6.71)
- V. C. Buildings. New England (Folder 6.72)
- V. C. Buildings. Noyes Hall (Folder 6.73)
- V. C. Buildings. Nursery School (Folder 6.74)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory (Folder 6.75)
- V. C. Buildings. Olmsted Hall of the Biological Sciences (Folder 6.76)
- V. C. Buildings. Palmer House (Folder 6.77)
- V. C. Buildings. Powerhouse, see also: Powerhouse Theatre (Hallie Flanagan Davis) (Folder 6.78)
- V. C. Buildings. Powerhouse Theatre (Hallie Flanagan Davis) (Folder 6.79)
- V. C. Buildings. Pratt House (Folder 6.80)
- V. C. Buildings. President's House (Folder 6.81)
- V. C. Buildings. Riding Hall and Calistenium, see: Avery
- V. C. Buildings. Rockefeller Hall (Folder 6.82)
- V. C. Buildings. Rombout (Folder 6.83)
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders Laboratory of Chemistry, see: Sanders biographical file
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders Classroom / Laboratory of Chemistry, see also: materials in Archives files (Folder 6.84a)
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders Laboratory of Physics, see also: materials in Archives files (Folder 6.84b)
- V. C. Buildings. Skinner (Folder 6.85)
- V. C. Buildings. Strong (Folder 6.86)
- V. C. Buildings. Students Building (ACDC) (Folder 6.87)
- V. C. Buildings. Swift (Folder 6.88)
- V. C. Buildings. Taylor (Folder 6.89)
- V. C. Buildings. Terrace Houses (Folder 6.90)
- V. C. Buildings. Thompson Library, see: V. C. Libraries. Building
- V. C. Buildings. Van Ingen (Folder 6.91)
- V. C. Buildings. Vassar Brothers Laboratory (Folder 6.92)
- V. C. Buildings. Walker Field House (Folder 6.93)
- V. C. Buildings. Warden's House, see: V.C. Buildings. Pratt House
- V. C. Buildings. Watson Faculty House (Jeannette K.) (Folder 6.94)
- V. C. Buildings. Williams (Folder 6.95)
- V. C. Business Administration (Folder 6.96)
- V. C. Calendar (about) (Folder 7.1)
- V. C. Calendar Days (Folder 7.2)
- V. C. Camera Club (Folder 7.3)
- V. C. Cameras (Folder 7.4)
- V. C. Campus (Folder 7.5-7.7)
- V. C. Campus. Committee for Master Planning (Folder 7.8)
- V. C. Campus. Council of Independent Colleges - Survey of Historic Architecture and Design (Folder 7.9)
- V. C. Campus. Forever Green Committee (Folder 7.10)
- V. C. Campus. Maps (Folder 7.11-7.12)
- V. C. Campus. Shakespeare Garden (Folder 7.13)
- V. C. Campus. Statues (Folder 7.14)
- V. C. Campus Activities, Office of (Folder 7.15)
- V. C. Campus Patrol, see: V. C. Security. Campus Patrol
- V. C. Capital Campaign, 1969-1972 (Folder 7.16-7.18)
- V. C. Capital Campaign, 1993- (Folder 7.19)
- V. C. Career Development and Field Work (Folder 7.20)
- V. C. Career Development and Field Work Newsletter and Action Line (Folder 7.21-7.22)
- V. C. Career Development and Field Work Newsletter and Job Line (Folder 7.23)
- V. C. Career Planning and Placement, Office of, see also: V. C. Vocational Bureau, Career Development and Field Work (Folder 7.24)
- V. C. Caricatures, see: V. C. Humor, caricatures, etc.
- V. C. Cartoons see: V. C. Humor, caricatures, etc.
- V. C. Catalogue (Folder 7.25)
- V. C. "Catlin Report", see also: V. C. Departments. Black Studies (Folder 7.26)
- V. C. Census Bureau (Folder 7.27)
- V. C. Centennial, see: V. C. Anniversaries, 100th
- V. C. Chairs, Endowed, see: V. C. Faculty. Chairs; Endowed
- V. C. Changing American Culture, see: V. C. Departments. American Culture
- V. C. Chapel Services, through 1968/1969 (Folder 7.28)
- V. C. Chapel Services, 1969/1970 (Folder 7.29)
- V. C. Chapel Services, 1980- (Folder 7.30)
- V. C. Chapel Tower. Books (Folder 7.31)
- V. C. Chaplains (individuals) (Folder 7.32)
- V. C. Chaplain's Office (to 1986/1987), see also: V. C. Office of Religious Activities and Chaplaincy Services (Folder 7.33)
- V. C. Charter (Folder 7.34)
- V. C. Charts (Folder 7.35)
- V. C. Chief Justice (Folder 7.36)
- V. C. China and Silver (Folder 7.37)
- V. C. Choir (Folder 7.38)
- V. C. Chorus (Folder 7.39)
- V. C. Christian Association (Folder 7.40-7.41)
- V. C. Christian Association. Publicity from the Settlement Houses, 1926-1932 (Folder 7.42)
- V. C. Christian Association. Correspondence relating to dolls and other donations, 1928-1933 (Folder 7.43)
- V. C. Christmas Card (Folder 7.44)
- V. C. Christmas Fair (Folder 7.45)
- V. C. Christmas Party (Folder 8.1)
- V. C. Christmas Traditions (Folder 8.2)
- V. C. Chronology (Great Experiment 1961) (Folder 8.3)
- V. C. Church Affiliation (Folder 8.4)
- V. C. Cinema '85 (Folder 8.5)
- V. C. Circle, see: V. C. Campus
- V. C. Citizens' Committee on Human Rights (Folder 8.6)
- V. C. Evalyn A. Clark Fund and Symposium (Folder 8.7)
- V. C. Class Attendance (Folder 8.8)
- V. C. Class Banners (Folder 8.9)
- V. C. Class Day (Folder 8.10)
- V. C. Class of 1880. Fund for old age welfare (Folder 8.11)
- V. C. Class of 1928. Fund for old age welfare (Folder 8.12)
- V. C. Class of 1933. Reunion Questionnaires (Folder 8.13)
- V. C. Class of 1942 (Folder 8.14)
- V. C. Class outlines (incomplete) (Folder 8.15)
- V. C. Class Photographs (Folder 8.16)
- V. C. Class Rings (Folder 8.17)
- V. C. Class Songs, see: V. C. Songs.
- V. C. Class Trees (Folder 8.18)
- V. C. Classical Museum, see: V. C. Museums. Classics
- V. C. Classroom, 1963 (Folder 8.19)
- V. C. Classroom, 1964 (Folder 8.20)
- V. C. Classroom, 1965 (Folder 8.21)
- V. C. Classroom, 1966 (Folder 8.22)
- V. C. Classroom, 1967 (Folder 8.23)
- V. C. Classroom, 1968 (Folder 8.24)
- V. C. Classroom, 1972 (Folder 8.25)
- V. C. Club Espanol (Folder 8.26)
- V. C. Club Francais (Folder 8.27)
- V. C. Club House News, see: V.C. Goodfellowship Club Collection
- V. C. Coal Bin Theater (Folder 8.27a)
- V. C. Coalition for Social Responsibility (additional documents in Archival Collection), see also: V. C. Trustees Investor Responsibility Committee, after 1981/1982 see: V. C. Vassar Progressive Union (Folder 8.28)
- V. C. Coeducation, see also: V. C. Veterans (Folder 8.29-8.32)
- V. C. Coeducation--Student exchange programs with men's colleges (Folder 8.32a)
- V. C. Cognitive Science Studies Groups (Folder 8.33)
- V. C. College Center, see: V. C. Buildings Main - College Center
- V. C. College Courses, see. V. C. Interdepartmental courses
- V. C. College Government Association, see also: V. C. Student Government Association (Folder 8.34-8.35)
- V. C. College Planning Council (Folder 8.36)
- V. C. College Regulations (Folder 8.37)
- V. C. College Relations, Office of, see also: V. C. Publications, Bureau of; V. C. Public Relations, Office of; V. C. News Office; V. C. Press and Information Office (Folder 8.38)
- V. C. College Settlements Association (Folder 8.39)
- V. C. College Settlements Association: Helen Noyes, notes on the history and membership of the Vassar chapter (Folder 8.39a)
- V. C. Collegiate Periodical League (Folder 8.40)
- V. C. Colors (Folder 8.41)
- V. C. Combined Drive, see: Community Chest, United Way, V. C. Vassar Drive
- V. C. Commencement, see also: Vassar College Baccalaureate and Commencement Records
- V. C. Commencement. General (Folder 8.42)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement Committee correspondence and Commencement Musical (Folder 8.43)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement Committee Chairman, 1857-1970 (Folder 8.44)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement programs, see also: Vassar College Baccalaureate and Commencement Records, 1867-2014
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement programs, 1867-1916 (Folder 8.45)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement programs, 1917-1938 (Folder 8.46)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement programs, 1939-1958 (Folder 8.47)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement programs, 1959-1967 (Folder 8.48)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement programs, 1968-1983 (Folder 8.49)
- V. C. Commencement. Commencement programs, 1984-1997 (Folder 8.50)
- [EMPTY] (Folder 8.51)
- V. C. Commencement. Faculty memos and correspondence (Folder 8.52)
- V. C. Commencement. names added to graduate lists, 1931-1995 (Folder 8.53)
- V. C. Commencement. Newspaper clippings, 1869-1993 (Folder 8.54)
- V. C. Commencement. Office of Public Relations, News Office, Press Information Office, 1851-1985 (Folder 8.55)
- V. C. Commencement. Office of Public Relations, News Office, Press Information Office, 1986-2000 (Folder 8.56)
- V. C. Commencement. Senior gift (Folder 8.57)
- V. C. Commencement. Speakers and speeches--General (Folder 8.58)
- V. C. Commencement. Speakers and speeches, Early-1930 (Folder 8.59)
- V. C. Commencement. Speakers and speeches, 1931-1950 (Folder 8.60)
- V. C. Commencement. Speakers and speeches, 1951-1960 (Folder 8.61)
- V C. Commencement. Speakers and speeches, 1961-1970 (Folder 8.62)
- V C. Commencement. Speakers and speeches, 1971- (Folder 8.63)
- V. C. Committee on Computing (Folder 8.64)
- V. C. Committee on Disability Issues (Folder 8.65)
- V. C. Communications, Dept. of (Folder 8.66)
- V. C. Communications, Office of (Folder 8.67)
- V. C. Communism, Accusations regarding (Folder 8.68)
- V. C. Community Church (for material after 1950, see: V. C. Community Religious Association) (Folder 8.69)
- V. C. Community Day (Folder 8.70)
- V. C. Community Relations, see: V. C. Poughkeepsie, Relations with
- V. C. Community Religious Association (see also: V. C. Community Church) (Folder 8.71)
- V. C. Community Service (Folder 8.72)
- V. C. Community Works (Folder 8.73)
- V. C. Comptroller's Office (Folder 8.74)
- V. C. Computer Center (Folder 8.75)
- V. C. Computers (Folder 8.76)
- V. C. Concerts and Recitals (Folder 9.1)
- V. C. Concerts and Recitals. Press Releases (Folder 9.2)
- V. C. Conferences. At Vassar College, 1877-1924 (Folder 9.3)
- V. C. Conferences. At Vassar College, 1925-1949 (Folder 9.4)
- V. C. Conferences. At Vassar College, 1950-1959 (Folder 9.5)
- V. C. Conferences. At Vassar College, 1960-1969 (Folder 9.6)
- V. C. Conferences. At Vassar College, 1970- (Folder 9.7)
- V. C. Conferences. Berkshire Conference, 1981 (Folder 9.8)
- V. C. Conferences. Berkshire Conference, 1993 (Folder 9.9)
- V. C. Conferences. Biographers' Art Conference, 1981 (Folder 9.10)
- V. C. Conferences. Children’s Book Conference, 1979 and 1980 (Folder 9.11)
- V. C. Consumers League, see also: V. C. Political Association (Folder 9.12)
- V. C. Convocation (Fall) (Folder 9.13a-9.13b)
- V. C. Convocation (Spring), see also: V. C. Senior Convocation (Spring) (Folder 9.13c)
- V. C. Convocation Addresses (Spring and Fall), 1941-1965 (Folder 9.14a)
- V. C. Convocation Addresses (Spring and Fall), 1966-2006 (Folder 9.14b)
- V. C. Convocation Addresses (Spring and Fall), 2009-2023 (Folder 9.14c)
- V. C. Cooperative Housing, see also: V. C. Buildings - Blodgett, Ferry, and Palmer (Folder 9.15)
- V. C. Cooperative System - after 1953, see: V. C. Student work system (Folder 9.16)
- V. C. Copy Center, see also: V. C. Stenographic Bureau (Folder 9.17)
- V. C. Cornaro Celebration, April 28 - 30, 1978 (Folder 9.18)
- V. C. Corridor Teachers (Folder 9.19)
- V. C. Counseling and Assistance in Response to Rape, see: V. C. Sexual Exploitation
- V. C. Counseling Service (Folder 9.20)
- V. C. Course of Study Pamphlet (Folder 9.21)
- V. C. Courses, see: V. C. Curriculum, V. C. Schedule of Classes
- V. C. Craft Shops (Folder 9.22)
- V. C. Cultural Arts Board (Folder 9.23)
- V. C. Curriculum, to 1942 (Folder 9.24)
- V. C. Curriculum, to 1942 (Folder 9.24a)
  (VC curriculum proposals)
- V. C. Curriculum, to 1942 (Folder 9.24b)
  (changes in courses, 1934)
- V. C. Curriculum, 1943-1946 (Folder 9.25)
- V. C. Curriculum, 1947-1969 (Folder 9.26)
- V. C. Curriculum, 1970- (Folder 9.27)
- V. C. Curriculum. Independent Study (Folder 9.28)
- V. C. Curriculum. Major Field (Folder 9.29)
- V. C. Curtis Lecture see: V. C. Library Curtis Lecture
- V. C. Customs, see: V. C. Traditions
- V. C. Cuts (for printing photographs) (Folder 9.30)
- V. C. D.A.R. Chapter (at Vassar College)(See also: Daughters of the American Revolution. Poughkeepsie Chapter) (Folder 9.31)
- V. C. D.A.R. Chapter (at Vassar College): record of the historian of the Vassar College Chapter, 1897 (Folder 9.31a)
- V. C. D.A.R. Chapter (at Vassar College): Charter of the Vassar College Chapter, 1897 Feb 18 (Oversize Box 1)
- V. C. Daisy Chain (Folder 9.32)
- V. C. Dana, Charles A., Award (re: Exploring Transfer Program) (Folder 9.33)
- V. C. Dana, Elizabeth E., Reading Prize (Folder 9.34)
- V. C. Dance concerts, see: V. C. Concerts; also names of dance groups
- V. C. Dancing (Folder 9.35)
- V. C. Daughters and Sons, see also: V. C. Granddaughters and Grandsons (Folder 9.36)
- V. C. Dean, through June 1961 (Folder 9.37)
- V. C. Dean of the College, 1980- (Folder 9.38)
- V. C. Dean of Faculty, July l, 1961 - June 1977 (Folder 9.39)
- V. C. Dean of Faculty, July 1977- (Folder 9.40)
- V. C. Dean of Freshmen (Folder 9.41)
- V. C. Dean of Residence (Folder 9.42)
- V. C. Dean of Student Life (Folder 9.43)
- V. C. Dean of Studies (Folder 9.44)
- V. C. Dean's Program (Folder 9.45)
- V. C. Debate (Folder 9.46)
- V. C. DeGrolier Prize (Folder 9.47)
- V. C. Degrees, see also: V. C. Commencement, V. C. Master's Degrees (Folder 9.48)
- V. C. Departments and Programs (General) (Folder 9.49-9.50)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Africana Studies (1976/77-, see also: V. C. Dept. Black Studies (1969-May 1976) (Folder 10.1)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Africana Studies. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.2)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. American Culture (Folder 10.3)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. American Culture. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.4)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Anthropology and Sociology, see also: Sociology; Economics, Sociology and Anthropology (Folder 10.5)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Anthropology and Sociology. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.6)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Art, see also: V. C. Art Collections, V. C. Art Exhibitions, V. C. Art Gallery (Folder 10.7)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Art. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.8)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Asian Studies, see also: V. C. East Asian Studies (Folder 10.9)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Asian Studies. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.10)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Astronomy (Folder 10.11)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Astronomy. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.12)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Biology, see also: V. C. Departments. Physiology, Plant Science, Zoology (Folder 10.13)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Biology. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.14)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Black Studies (1969-1975/76), see also: Africana Studies (Folder 10.15-10.18)
- EMPTY (Folder 10.19)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Botany, see: V. C. Dept Plant Science
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Chemistry (Folder 10.20)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Chemistry. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.21)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Child Study, see also: V. C. Departments Psychology (Folder 10.22)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Child Study. Film Program (Folder 10.23)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Child Study. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.24)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Classics (Folder 10.25)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Classics. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.26)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Cognitive Science (Folder 10.27)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Cognitive Science. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.28)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Computer Science (Folder 10.29)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Computer Science. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.30)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Conservation, Division of (Folder 10.31)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Conservation, Division of. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.32)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Drama (Folder 10.33-10.34)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Drama. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.35)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. East Asian Studies, see: V. C. East Asian Studies
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Economics, Sociology, and Anthropology, see also: V. C. Departments and Programs. Anthropology and Sociology (Folder 10.36)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Economics (Folder 10.37)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Economics. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.38)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Education (Folder 10.39)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Education. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.40)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. English (Folder 10.41)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. English, Oral (Folder 10.42)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. English. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.43)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Euthenics Division (Folder 10.44 -10.45)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Euthenics Division, Clippings, (photocopies) (Folder 10.46)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Euthenics Division, Correspondence (Folder 10.47)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Euthenics Division. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.48)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. French, see also: V. C. Departments and Programs. Modern Languages (Folder 10.49)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. French. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.50)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Geography (Folder 10.51)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Geography. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.52)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Geology (Folder 10.53)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Geology. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.54)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. German, see also: V. C. Departments and Programs. Modern Languages (Folder 10.55)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. German. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.56)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Greek, see: V. C. Departments and Programs. Classics
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Health (Folder 10.57)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Health. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.58)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Hispanic Studies (Folder 10.59)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Hispanic Studies. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.60)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. History (Folder 10.61-10.62)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. History. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.63)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. History 105 (Folder 10.64)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Italian, see also: V. C. Departments and Programs. Modern Languages (Folder 10.65)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Italian. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.66)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Latin, see: V. C. Departments and Programs. Classics
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Latin American Studies (Folder 10.67)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Latin American Studies. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.68)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Mathematics (Folder 10.69)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Mathematics. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 10.70)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Modern Languages (Folder 10.70)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Music (Folder 11.1)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Music. Calendars of events (Folder 11.2)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Music. Course outlines (Folder 11.3)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Music. Marston Concerts (Folder 11.4)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Music. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.5)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Music Teachers Letters (1864 - 1867), see: Autograph file: Small, Tryon, Griggs, Wiebe, Shinn.
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Philosophy (Folder 11.6)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Philosophy. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.7)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physical education, 1862–1939 (Folder 11.8)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physical education, 1940-1979 (Folder 11.9)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physical education, 1980- (Folder 11.10)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physical Education (Printed history materials) (Folder 11.11)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physical Education. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.12)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physics (Folder 11.13)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physics. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.14)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physiology (Folder 11.15)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Physiology. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.16)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Plant Science (Folder 11.17)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Plant Science. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.18)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Political Science (Folder 11.19)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Political Science. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.20)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Political Science. Model Cities (Folder 11.21)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Psychology, see also: V. C. Departments and Programs. Child Study (Folder 11.22)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Psychology. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.23)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Religion (Folder 11.24)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Religion. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.25)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Russian, see also: V. C. Evening Russian Program (Folder 11.26)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Russian. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.27)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Science, Technology and Society, see: V. C. Science, Technology and Society Program
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Sociology 1981/1982, see also: V. C. Departments and Programs. Anthropology and Sociology (Folder 11.28)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Sociology. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.29)